[
  {
    "question": "انجيلو",
    "answer": "انجيلو"
  },
  {
    "question": "اثي",
    "answer": "اثي"
  },
  {
    "question": "فيودور",
    "answer": "فيودور"
  },
  {
    "question": "كيندر",
    "answer": "كيندر"
  },
  {
    "question": "اكاي",
    "answer": "اكاي"
  },
  {
    "question": "فينوم",
    "answer": "فينوم"
  },
  {
    "question": "شادو",
    "answer": "شادو"
  },
  {
    "question": "ارليكينو",
    "answer": "ارليكينو"
  },
  {
    "question": "هوتاو",
    "answer": "هوتاو"
  },
  {
    "question": "الهيثم",
    "answer": "الهيثم"
  },
  {
    "question": "دازاي",
    "answer": "دازاي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناروتو",
    "answer": "ناروتو"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساسكي",
    "answer": "ساسكي"
  },
  {
    "question": "يوكي",
    "answer": "يوكي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايرين",
    "answer": "ايرين"
  },
  {
    "question": "موزان",
    "answer": "موزان"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميكاسا",
    "answer": "ميكاسا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ارمين",
    "answer": "ارمين"
  },
  {
    "question": "ذيك",
    "answer": "ذيك"
  },
  {
    "question": "هانجي",
    "answer": "هانجي"
  },
  {
    "question": "اكازا",
    "answer": "اكازا"
  },
  {
    "question": "دوما",
    "answer": "دوما"
  },
  {
    "question": "موزان",
    "answer": "موزان"
  },
  {
    "question": "غيو",
    "answer": "غيو"
  },
  {
    "question": "شينوبو",
    "answer": "شينوبو"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايثديث",
    "answer": "ايثديث"
  },
  {
    "question": "اكامي",
    "answer": "اكامي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايساغي",
    "answer": "ايساغي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناغي",
    "answer": "ناغي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساي",
    "answer": "ساي"
  },
  {
    "question": "سيل",
    "answer": "سيل"
  },
  {
    "question": "رين",
    "answer": "رين"
  },
  {
    "question": "كونان",
    "answer": "كونان"
  },
  {
    "question": "روجر",
    "answer": "روجر"
  },
  {
    "question": "زورو",
    "answer": "زورو"
  },
  {
    "question": "الفا",
    "answer": "الفا"
  },
  {
    "question": "بيتا",
    "answer": "بيتا"
  },
  {
    "question": "تسونادي",
    "answer": "تسونادي"
  },
  {
    "question": "جيرايا",
    "answer": "جيرايا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كانيكي",
    "answer": "كانيكي"
  },
  {
    "question": "انجيلا",
    "answer": "انجيلا"
  },
  {
    "question": "اياتو",
    "answer": "اياتو"
  },
  {
    "question": "شاو",
    "answer": "شاو"
  },
  {
    "question": "يوو",
    "answer": "يوو"
  },
  {
    "question": "توموري",
    "answer": "توموري"
  },
  {
    "question": "روديوس",
    "answer": "روديوس"
  },
  {
    "question": "سكاراموش",
    "answer": "سكاراموش"
  },
  {
    "question": "ارثر",
    "answer": "ارثر"
  }
]
